Rick Whitesell Record Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 2. 12" Discs, 2; 17 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 25 Folders: 2.12.1 - 2.12.809
  - Jimmie Rodgers, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LPM-2865 (Folder 542, Box 17)
    - My Time Ain't Long
  - Sonny Rollins, Record Label: Milestone; Label Number: M 9098 (Folder 543, Box 17)
    - Love At First Sight
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 544, Box 17)
  - Diana Ross&The Supremes, Record Label: Motown; Label Number: MS 689 (Folder 545, Box 17)
    - Let The Sunshine In
  - Tom Rush, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: KC 31306 (Folder 546, Box 17)
    - Merrimack County
  - Tom Rush, Record Label: Elektra; Label Number: EKS-74018 (Folder 547, Box 17)
    - The Circle Game
  - Tom Rush, Record Label: Elektra; Label Number: EKL-308 (Folder 548, Box 17)
    - Take A Little Walk With Me
  - Bobby Rydell, Record Label: Cameo; Label Number: LP 1006 (Folder 549, Box 17)
    - We Got Love
  - Bobby Rydell, Record Label: Cameo; Label Number: C 1009 (Folder 550, Box 17)
    - Bobby's Biggest Hits
  - Bobby Rydell, Record Label: Cameo; Label Number: C 4017 (Folder 551, Box 17)
    - An Era Reborn
  - Kyu Sakamoto, Record Label: Capitol; Label Number: T 10349 (Folder 552, Box 17)
    - Sukiyaki
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 553, Box 17)
  - Don Sampson, Record Label: Revolver; Label Number: R 101 (Folder 554, Box 17)
    - American Songs
  - Tommy Sands, Record Label: Capitol; Label Number: T 848 (Folder 555, Box 17)
    - Steady Date
  - Jan Savitt, Record Label: Ajax; Label Number: LP-113 (Folder 556, Box 17)
    - In Disco Order, Volume 1
  - Neil Sedaka&The Tokens&The Coins, Record Label: Crown; Label Number: CST 641 (Folder 557, Box 17)
    - Neil Sedaka
  - Pete Seeger, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: CS 9134 (Folder 558, Box 18)
    - Strangers And Cousins
  - Pete Seeger, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: CS 9416 (Folder 559, Box 18)
    - Pete Seeger's Greatest Hits
  - Pete Seeger, Record Label: Folkways; Label Number: C 7526 (Folder 560, Box 18)
    - Song And Play Time
  - Dee Dee Sharp, Record Label: Cameo; Label Number: C 1018 (Folder 561, Box 18)
    - It's Mashed Potato Time
  - Dee Dee Sharp, Record Label: Cameo; Label Number: C 1050 (Folder 562, Box 18)
    - Do The Bird
  - Artie Shaw And His Orchestra, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LPM-1244 (Folder 563, Box 18)
    - LPM-1244
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 564, Box 18)
  - The Shirelles, Record Label: Scepter; Label Number: 507 (Folder 565, Box 18)
    - The Shirelles Greatest Hits
  - Horace Silver Quintet, Record Label: Epic; Label Number: LA 16005 (Folder 566, Box 18)
    - Silver's Blue
  - Simaryp, Record Label: Trojan; Label Number: TRLS-187 (Folder 567, Box 18)
    - Skinhead Moonstomp
  - Nina Simone, Record Label: Bethlehem; Label Number: BCP-6003 (Folder 568, Box 18)
    - The Finest Of Nina Simone - I Loves You Porgy
  - Nina Simone, Record Label: Colpix; Label Number: SCP 419 (Folder 569, Box 18)
    - Forbidden Fruit
  - Nina Simone, Record Label: Philips; Label Number: PHM-200-135 (Folder 570, Box 18)
    - Nina Simone In Concert
  - Nina Simone, Record Label: RCA; Label Number: APL1-0241 (Folder 571, Box 18)
    - It Is Finished
  - Zoot Sims, Record Label: Jazzland; Label Number: JLP-2 (Folder 572, Box 18)
    - Quintet
  - Zoot Sims, Record Label: Pablo; Label Number: 2310-700 (Folder 573, Box 18)
    - Soprano Sax
  - Zoot Sims, Record Label: Pablo; Label Number: 2310-744 (Folder 574, Box 18)
    - Zoot Sims And The Gershwin Brothers
  - Jimmy Smith, Record Label: Verve; Label Number: V-8641 (Folder 575, Box 18)
    - Got My Mojo Workin'
  - Jimmy Smith, Record Label: Verve; Label Number: V-8667 (Folder 576, Box 18)
    - Hoochie Cooche Man
  - Jimmy Smith, Record Label: Verve; Label Number: V6-652-2 (Folder 577, Box 18)
    - 24 Karat Hits
  - Willis "The Lion" Smith, Record Label: Mainstream; Label Number: 56027 (Folder 578, Box 18)
    - A Legend
  - The Sons Of The Pioneers, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LPM-2603 (Folder 579, Box 18)
    - Our Men Out West
  - Rosalie Sorrels, Record Label: Green Linnet; Label Number: SIF-1024 (Folder 580, Box 18)
    - The Lonesome Roving Wolves
  - The Soul Stirrers featuring Sam Cooke, Record Label: Specialty; Label Number: SP 2106 (Folder 581, Box 18)
    - The Soul Stirrers
  - Eddie South, Record Label: Chess; Label Number: CHV 415 (Folder 582, Box 18)
    - South-Side Jazz
  - The Stanley Brothers, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20349 (Folder 583, Box 18)
    - Country Pickin' and Singin'
  - The Staple Singers, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: LE 10190 (Folder 584, Box 18)
    - Amen!
  - Dakota Staton, Record Label: Capitol; Label Number: T 876 (Folder 585, Box 18)
    - The Late, Late Show
  - Dakota Staton, Record Label: Capitol; Label Number: T 1170 (Folder 586, Box 19)
    - Crazy He Calls Me
  - Steel Pulse, Record Label: Mango; Label Number: MLPS-9502 (Folder 587, Box 19)
    - Handsworth Revolution
  - Steel Pulse, Record Label: Mango; Label Number: MLPS-9568 (Folder 588, Box 19)
    - Tribute To The Martyrs
  - Steel Pulse, Record Label: Mango; Label Number: MLPS-9613 (Folder 589, Box 19)
    - Reggae Fever
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 590, Box 19)
  - Sonny Stitt/Zoot Sims, Record Label: Chess; Label Number: 2ACMJ-406 (Folder 591, Box 19)
    - Interaction
  - Joe Sun, Record Label: Ovation; Label Number: OV 1755 (Folder 592, Box 19)
    - Livin' On Honky Tonk Time
  - Sugar Daddy, Record Label: disco music; Label Number: (Folder 593, Box 19)
    - Another One Bites The Dust - rap
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 594, Box 19)
  - The Supremes, Record Label: Motown; Label Number: 636 (Folder 595, Box 19)
    - At The Copa
  - The Surfaris, Record Label: Dot; Label Number: DLP 3535 (Folder 596, Box 19)
    - Wipe Out&Surfer Joe
  - The Swallows, Record Label: King; Label Number: KLP 500 (Folder 597, Box 19)
    - The Best Of The Swallows
  - The Swan Silvertones, Record Label: Creed; Label Number: 3043 (Folder 598, Box 19)
    - What's the Matter Now
  - The Swan Silvertones, Record Label: Gusto; Label Number: K-5022X (Folder 599, Box 19)
    - Swan's Silvertone Singers' Greatest Hits
  - The Swan Silvertones, Record Label: Specialty; Label Number: SPS-2122 (Folder 600, Box 19)
    - Love Lifted Me
  - The Swan Silvertones, Record Label: Vee-Jay; Label Number: LP 5003 (Folder 601, Box 19)
    - The Swan Silvertones
  - The Swan Silvertones, Record Label: Up Front; Label Number: UPF 141 (Folder 602, Box 19)
    - The Swan Silvertones
  - The Swanee Quinete, Record Label: Nashboro; Label Number: LP 7014 (Folder 603, Box 19)
    - Meetin' Tonight
  - The Tamlins, Record Label: J&J; Label Number: JJ-021 (Folder 604, Box 19)
    - Greatest Hits
  - Art Tatum, Record Label: Alamac; Label Number: QRS 2402 (Folder 605, Box 19)
    - Classic Solos
  - Art Tatum, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: CS 9655 (Folder 606, Box 19)
    - Piano Starts Here
  - Art Tatum, Record Label: Verve; Label Number: MG V-8036 (Folder 607, Box 19)
    - The Genius Of Art Tatum # 1
  - Johnnie Taylor, Record Label: Stax; Label Number: STS-2032 (Folder 608, Box 19)
    - Johnnie Taylor's Greatest Hits
  - Sam "The Man" Taylor, Record Label: Decca; Label Number: DL 4302 (Folder 609, Box 19)
    - Misty Mood
  - Sam "The Man" Taylor, Record Label: MGM; Label Number: E 3292 (Folder 610, Box 19)
    - Blue Mist
  - Jack Teagarden&His Orchestra, Record Label: Jazztone; Label Number: J-1222 (Folder 611, Box 19)
    - Big T
  - Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Record Label: Crown; Label Number: CLP 5236 (Folder 612, Box 19)
    - Sister Rosetta Tharpe
  - Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Record Label: MCA; Label Number: 510 148 (Folder 613, Box 19)
    - Soul Sister 1946 - 1949
  - Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Record Label: MCA; Label Number: 510 056 (Folder 614, Box 19)
    - Gospel Train
  - Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20201 (Folder 615, Box 19)
    - Gospel Train
  - Sister Rosetta Tharpe, Record Label: Spinorama; Label Number: MK 3072 (Folder 616, Box 19)
    - Spirituals In Rhythm
  - Sister Rosetta Tharpe and Marie Knight, Record Label: MCA; Label Number: 510 129 (Folder 617, Box 19)
    - Gospel Songs 1951-1956
  - Third World, Record Label: Island; Label Number: ILPS 9616 (Folder 618, Box 20)
    - Prisoner In The Street
  - Leon Thomas, Record Label: Flying Dutchman; Label Number: FD 10167 (Folder 619, Box 20)
    - Full Circle
  - Joe Thomas, Record Label: Groove Merchant; Label Number: GM 504 (Folder 620, Box 20)
    - Joy Of Cookin'
  - Hank Thompson, Record Label: Famous Twinset; Label Number: PAS2-1041 (Folder 621, Box 20)
    - PAS2-1041
  - Toots And The Maytals, Record Label: Dragon; Label Number: DRLS-5004 (Folder 622, Box 20)
    - In The Dark
  - Toots And The Maytals, Record Label: Mango; Label Number: MLPS 9590 (Folder 623, Box 20)
    - Just Like That
  - Peter Tosh, Record Label: Rolling Stones; Label Number: COC 39109 (Folder 624, Box 20)
    - Bush Doctor
  - Henry Townsend, Record Label: Nighthawk; Label Number: 201 (Folder 625, Box 20)
    - Mule
  - The Trammps, Record Label: Atlantic; Label Number: SD 19194 (Folder 626, Box 20)
    - The Best Of The Trammps
  - Ike And Tina Turner, Record Label: Warner Bros.; Label Number: 1579 (Folder 627, Box 20)
    - The Ike And Tina Turner Show Live!
  - Ike And Tina Turner, Record Label: Minit; Label Number: LP-24018 (Folder 628, Box 20)
    - In Person
  - Charles Tyler Ensemble, Record Label: ESP-Disk; Label Number: 1029 (Folder 629, Box 20)
    - Charles Tyler Ensemble
  - The Tymes, Record Label: Parkway; Label Number: P-7032 (Folder 630, Box 20)
    - So Much In Love
  - The Tymes, Record Label: Parkway; Label Number: P-7038 (Folder 631, Box 20)
    - The Sound Of The Wonderful Tymes
  - Vanilla Fudge, Record Label: Atco; Label Number: SD 33-224 (Folder 632, Box 20)
    - Vanilla Fudge
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 633, Box 20)
  - Vanilla Fudge, Record Label: Atco; Label Number: SD 33-244 (Folder 634, Box 20)
    - Renaissance
  - Vanilla Fudge, Record Label: Atco; Label Number: SD 33-278 (Folder 635, Box 20)
    - Near The Beginning
  - Sarah Vaughan, Record Label: Coronet; Label Number: CX-277 (Folder 636, Box 20)
    - Belts The Hits
  - Sarah Vaughan, Record Label: Everest; Label Number: FS 250 (Folder 637, Box 20)
    - Sarah Vaughan With Guest Artists: Bud Powell, Charlie, Parker, Dizzy Gollespie, Teddy Wilson, Billy Taylor, Don Byas, J.C. Heard
  - Sarah Vaughan, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20383 (Folder 638, Box 20)
    - After Hours At The London House
  - Sarah Vaughan, Record Label: Maxi; Label Number: MAXI 111 (Folder 639, Box 20)
    - Sarah Vaughan
  - The Velons, Record Label: Maxi; Label Number: MAXI 111 (Folder 640, Box 20)
    - Remember When
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 641, Box 20)
  - Eddie Vinson, Record Label: Delmark; Label Number: DS 631 (Folder 642, Box 20)
    - Kidney Stew Is Fine
  - The Wailers, Record Label: Etiquette; Label Number: ET-ALBS-026 (Folder 643, Box 20)
    - Out Of Our Tree
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 644, Box 20)
  - Fats Waller, Record Label: DJM; Label Number: DJD 28003 (Folder 645, Box 20)
    - All That Jazz
  - Fats Waller, Record Label: Olympic; Label Number: 7106 (Folder 646, Box 20)
    - The Fats Waller Legacy
  - Fats Waller, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LPM-1502 (Folder 647, Box 20)
    - Handful Of Keys
  - Fats Waller, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LPV-550 (Folder 648, Box 20)
    - Smashing Thirds
  - The Famous Ward Singers, Record Label: Savoy; Label Number: MG 14001 (Folder 649, Box 20)
    - Surely God Is Able
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: EmArcy; Label Number: MG 25119 (Folder 650, Box 21)
    - Sings Fats Waller
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Grand Award; Label Number: 33-318 (Folder 651, Box 21)
    - Sings The Blues
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20119 (Folder 652, Box 21)
    - Music For A First Love
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20572 (2 copies) (Folder 653, Box 21)
    - Unforgettable
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20614 (Folder 654, Box 21)
    - For Lonely Lovers
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20638 (2 copies) (Folder 655, Box 21)
    - September In The Rain
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Pickwick; Label Number: SPC-3043 (Folder 656, Box 21)
    - Dinah Washington
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Trip; Label Number: TLP-5516 (Folder 657, Box 21)
    - After Hours With Miss "D" 1955
  - Dinah Washington, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20479 (Folder 658, Box 21)
    - What A Diff'rence A Day Makes
  - Geno Washington, Record Label: DJM; Label Number: DFJ 20561 (Folder 659, Box 21)
    - That's Why Hollywood Loves Me
  - Weather Report, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: KC 32210 (Folder 660, Box 21)
    - Sweetnighter
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 661, Box 21)
  - We Five, Record Label: A&M; Label Number: LP 111 (Folder 662, Box 21)
    - You Were On My Mind
  - We Five, Record Label: A&M; Label Number: SP 4138 (Folder 663, Box 21)
    - Make Someone Happy
  - Kitty Wells, Record Label: Decca; Label Number: DXSB 7174 (Folder 664, Box 21)
    - The Kitty Wells Story
  - West Side Story, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: S 32603 (Folder 665, Box 21)
    - Original Broadway Cast
  - Buck White&The Down Home Folks, Record Label: Sugar Hill; Label Number: SH 3703 (Folder 666, Box 21)
    - Poor Folks Pleasure
  - Josh White, Record Label: Mercury; Label Number: MG 20821 (Folder 667, Box 21)
    - The Beginning, Volume 2
  - Josh White, Jr., Record Label: Mountain Railroad; Label Number: MR 52791 (Folder 668, Box 21)
    - In Concert - Sing A Rainbow
  - Joy White, Record Label: Revolutionary Sounds; Label Number: KR-016 (Folder 669, Box 21)
    - Sentimental Reasons
  - The Wild Tchoupitoulas, Record Label: Island; Label Number: ILPS-9360 (Folder 670, Box 21)
    - Wild Tchoupitoulas
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 671, Box 21)
  - Billy Williams, Record Label: MGM; Label Number: E 3400 (Folder 672, Box 21)
    - The Billy Williams Quartet
  - Hank Williams, Record Label: MGM; Label Number: SE 4755-2 (Folder 673, Box 21)
    - 24 Of Hank Williams' Greatest Hits
  - Joe Williams, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LPM-2879 (Folder 674, Box 21)
    - Me And The Blues
  - John Williams, Record Label: EmArcy; Label Number: G 36061 (Folder 675, Box 21)
    - The John Williams Trio
  - Mary Lou Williams, Record Label: Folkways; Label Number: FJ 2860 (Folder 676, Box 21)
    - The History Of Jazz
  - Mary Lou Williams, Record Label: Folkways; Label Number: FA 2966 (Folder 677, Box 22)
    - The Asch Recordings, 1944-47
  - Otis Williams And His Charms, Record Label: King; Label Number: 5015X (Folder 678, Box 22)
    - 16 Hits
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 679, Box 22)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 680, Box 22)
  - Pam Windo And The Shades, Record Label: Bearsville; Label Number: BRK 3479 (Folder 681, Box 22)
    - Pam Windo And The Shades
  - Wings Over Jordan Choir, Record Label: Gusto; Label Number: K-5021x (Folder 682, Box 22)
    - Original Greatest Hits
  - Paul Winter Sextet, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: CL 2064 (Folder 683, Box 22)
    - New Jazz On Campus
  - The Wiz, Record Label: Atlantic; Label Number: SD 18137 (Folder 684, Box 22)
    - Broadway Musical
  - Bobby Womack, Record Label: United Artists; Label Number: LA 346-G (Folder 685, Box 22)
    - Bobby Womack's Greatest Hits
  - Stevie Wonder, Record Label: Tamla; Label Number: TS 291 (Folder 686, Box 22)
    - For Once In My Life
  - Reverend Maceo Woods, Record Label: Vee-Jay; Label Number: VJ-5067 (Folder 687, Box 22)
    - Sometimes I'm Happy, Sometimes I'm Sad
  - Billy Wright, Record Label: Route 66; Label Number: KIX-13 (Folder 688, Box 22)
    - Stacked Deck
  - O.V. Wright, Record Label: Cream; Label Number: HLP-6001 (Folder 689, Box 22)
    - Into Something - Can't Shake Loose
  - O.V. Wright, Record Label: Peacock; Label Number: LP-66 (Folder 690, Box 22)
    - 8 Men And 4 Women
  - Glenn Yarbrough, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LPM-3539 (Folder 691, Box 22)
    - The Lonely Things
  - Glenn Yarbrough, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LSP-3801 (Folder 692, Box 22)
    - For Emily, Whenever I May Find Her
  - Paramahansa Yogananda, Record Label: Self-Realization; Label Number: 121 (Folder 693, Box 22)
    - Chants And Prayers
  - Paramahansa Yogananda, Record Label: Self-Realization; Label Number: 103 (Folder 694, Box 22)
    - When Thy Song Flows Through Me
  - Paramahansa Yogananda, Record Label: Self-Realization; Label Number: 204 (Folder 695, Box 22)
    - I Will Be Thine Always
  - Paramahansa Yogananda, Record Label: Self-Realization; Label Number: 251 (Folder 696, Box 22)
    - In The Land Beyond My Dreams
  - Paramahansa Yogananda, Record Label: Self-Realization; Label Number: 301 (Folder 697, Box 22)
    - Is Meditation On God Compatible With Modern Life?
  - Great Moments In Jazz Re-Created At The Newport Jazz Festival, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: LSP-3369 (Folder 698, Box 22)
    - various artists
  - Giants Of Jazz, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: CL-1970 (Folder 699, Box 22)
    - various artists
  - Gems Of Jazz, Volume 5, Record Label: Decca; Label Number: DL 8043 (Folder 700, Box 22)
    - Art Hodes&His Orchestra
    - Jimmie McPartland&His Orchestra
    - Jimmie Noone&His Orchestra
  - Jazz Poll Winners, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: CS 8410 (Folder 701, Box 22)
    - various artists
  - Jazz Gala Concert, Record Label: Atlantic; Label Number: SD 1693 (Folder 702, Box 22)
    - Nat Adderly
    - Stan Getz
    - Gerry Mulligan
    - Jean "Toots" Thielemans
  - Jazz Of Two Decades, Record Label: EmArcy; Label Number: DEM-2 (Folder 703, Box 22)
    - Jazz Of The 40's - various artists
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 704, Box 22)
  - Encyclopedia Of Jazz On Records, Volume 4, Record Label: Decca; Label Number: DL 8401 (Folder 705, Box 22)
    - intentionally skipped
  - Encyclopedia Of Jazz In The 70's, Record Label: RCA; Label Number: APL2-1984 (Folder 706, Box 23)
    - various artists
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 707, Box 23)
  - New American Music, Record Label: Folkways; Label Number: FTS 33901 (Folder 708, Box 23)
    - New York Section Composers of the 1970's
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 709, Box 23)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 710, Box 23)
  - Golden Jazz, Record Label: Parker; Label Number: PLP-140 (Folder 711, Box 23)
    - Charlie Parker, Miles Davis, Yusef Lateff, Lester Young, Grant Green,&Cozy Cole
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 712, Box 23)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 713, Box 23)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 714, Box 23)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 715, Box 23)
  - The Count Basie Band With Joe Williams and The Dizzy Gillespie Band At Newport, Record Label: Verve; Label Number: V/v6-8560 (Folder 716, Box 23)
  - Charlie Christian&Wardell Gray, Record Label: Fran Staterna; Label Number: CG (Folder 717, Box 23)
    - Tribute From Sweden
  - Stan Getz&J.J. Johnson, Record Label: Verve; Label Number: MG V-8265 (Folder 718, Box 23)
    - At The Opera House
  - John Coltrane&Hank Mobley with Donald Byrd, Record Label: Prestige; Label Number: PR 7043 (Folder 719, Box 23)
    - Two Tenors
  - Stan Getz&Horace Silver, Record Label: Baronet; Label Number: B-102 (Folder 720, Box 23)
    - Pair Of Kings
  - Gary Burton&Stephane Grappelli, Record Label: Atlantic; Label Number: SD 1597 (Folder 721, Box 23)
    - Paris Encounter
  - Michel Legrand&Miles Davis, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: CL 1250 (Folder 722, Box 23)
    - Legrand Jazz
  - Gary McFarland&Gabor Szabo, Record Label: Impulse; Label Number: A-9122 (Folder 723, Box 23)
    - Simpático
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 724, Box 23)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 725, Box 23)
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 726, Box 23)
  - 50 Years Of Jazz Guitar, Record Label: Columbia; Label Number: 33566 (Folder 727, Box 23)
    - 24 Great Jazz Guitarists
  - Fun On The Frets - Early Jazz Guitar, Record Label: Yazoo; Label Number: 1061 (Folder 728, Box 23)
    - featuring Carl Kress, Tony Mottola, Dick McDonough, &George Van Eps
  - Chevrolet Golden Anniversary Album, Record Label: RCA Victor; Label Number: PR 111 (Folder 729, Box 23)
    - Louis Armstrong, Benny Goodman, Guy Lombardo, Duke Ellington, &others
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 730, Box 23)
  - The Finest of the Folk Bluesmen, Record Label: Bethlehem; Label Number: BCP-6017 (Folder 731, Box 23)
    - various artists
  - Hard Times, Record Label: Rounder; Label Number: 4007 (Folder 732, Box 23)
    - various folk-blues artists
  - Been Here And Gone - Music From The South, Volume 10, Record Label: Folkways; Label Number: FA 2659 (Folder 733, Box 23)
    - various artists
  - Brownie McGhee&Sonny Terry, Record Label: Everest; Label Number: FS-242 (Folder 734, Box 23)
    - Brownie&Sonny
  - Georgia Blues, Record Label: Rounder; Label Number: 2008 (Folder 735, Box 23)
    - various artists
  - Treasure Album, Record Label: Hickory; Label Number: LPS-154 (Folder 736, Box 23)
    - various folk artists
  - Religious Music - Congregational&Ceremonial, Record Label: Library of Congress; Label Number: LBC-1 (Folder 737, Box 23)
    - various artists
  - Fisk University Jubilee Quartet Old Black Joe Reverend J.A. Myers, Record Label: 78 rpm Victor; Label Number: 35097 (2 copies) (Folder 738, Box 23)
    - When Malindy Sings
  - Birmingham Quartet Anthology, Record Label: Clanka Lanka; Label Number: Cl-144,001/002 (Folder 739, Box 23)
    - Jefferson County, Alabama 1926 - 1953 various artists
  - The Gospel Book 1927 - 1953, Record Label: MCA; Label Number: 510 187 (Folder 740, Box 23)
    - various artists
  - Spirituals and Gospel Songs - The Lord's Servants 1944-1953, Record Label: MCA; Label Number: 510 197 (Folder 741, Box 24)
    - Rosetta Tharpe, Marie Knight, Vivian Cooper, Katie-Bell Nubin,&The Sisters of Song
  - Original Greatest Gospel Hits, Record Label: Gusto; Label Number: K-5023X (Folder 742, Box 24)
    - various artists
  - The Million Dollar Gospel collection, Record Label: Candlelite; Label Number: 2-263/4/5/6 (Folder 743, Box 24)
    - various artists
  - Newport Folk Festival 1964 - Evening Concerts, Volume 2, Record Label: Vanguard; Label Number: VSD-79185 (Folder 744, Box 24)
    - various artists
  - The Folk Scene, Record Label: Elektra; Label Number: SMP-6 (Folder 745, Box 24)
    - various artists
  - The Folk Song Tradition, Record Label: Tradition; Label Number: TSP 2 (Folder 746, Box 24)
    - various artists
  - Something To Sing About, Record Label: Milton Okun; Label Number: MOS 1D (Folder 747, Box 24)
    - Tom Paxton, Phil Ochs, Jack Elliott, Joan Baez, John Denver, Mary Travers, Paul Stookey, Peter Yarrow,&others
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label:; Label Number: (Folder 748, Box 24)
  - Bill Shute&Lisa Null, Record Label: Green Linnet; Label Number: SIF 1025 (2 copies) (Folder 749, Box 24)